1. randomEmail = custom.RandomData.generateRandomEmail()
5. randomFirstName = custom.RandomData.generateRandomFirstName()
9. randomLastName = custom.RandomData.generateRandomLastName()
13. randomPhone = custom.RandomData.generateRandomPhone()
17. randomAddress = custom.RandomData.generateRandomAddress()
21. randomCode = custom.RandomData.generateRandomCode()
25. openBrowser(URL)
29. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/header_digibox"))
33. click(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/icon-search"))
37. setText(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/field-search"), "IPHONE 11 PRO 128 GB DEEP PURPLE")
41. sendKeys(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/field-search"), Keys.chord(ENTER))
45. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/verify-product-iphone-11-pro"))
49. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/btn-product"))
53. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/button_Add to Cart"))
57. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/i_icon-cart"), 10)
61. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/i_icon-cart"))
65. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/btn_checkout"))
69. click(findTestObject("Checkout/btn_checkout"))
73. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Checkout guest/field_email"), 10)
77. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Checkout guest/field_email"), randomEmail)
81. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Checkout guest/btn_continue"))
85. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/field_First Name"), 10)
89. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/field_First Name"), randomFirstName)
93. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/field_Last Name"), randomLastName)
97. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/field_mobile phone"), randomPhone)
101. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/field_Address"), randomAddress)
105. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/input_ZipPostal Code"), randomCode)
109. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/input_Province"))
113. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/li_Phnom Penh Capital_Province"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
117. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/input_Select Province"))
121. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/li_Khan Chamkar Mon_Select_Province"))
125. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/input_Districts"))
129. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/li_Sangkat Tonle Basak_Districts"))
133. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/btn-save"))
137. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/btn-change"), 2)
141. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/btn-change"), 6)
145. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/btn-change"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
149. takeScreenshot()
153. updateAddress = custom.RandomData.generateRandomAddress()
157. updateCode = custom.RandomData.generateRandomCode()
161. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/field_Address"), 10)
165. clearText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/field_Address"))
169. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/field_Address"), updateAddress)
173. clearText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/input_ZipPostal Code"))
177. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/input_ZipPostal Code"), updateCode)
181. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/btn-save"))
185. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/btn-change"), 2)
189. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/btn-change"), 10)
193. takeScreenshot()
197. comment("Email      : " + randomEmail)
201. comment("First Name : " + randomFirstName)
205. comment("Last Name  : " + randomLastName)
209. comment("Phone      : " + randomPhone)
213. comment("Address    : " + randomAddress)
217. comment("Code    : " + randomCode)
221. comment("Updated Address : " + updateAddress)
225. comment("Updated Code    : " + updateCode)
229. closeBrowser()